Deepak Kaushik Plot no C-33 Flat G-3 Manglam city, Kalwar road Jaipur(Rajasthan)-302012 Phone no-7296949572

Professional Summary

Knowledgeable and dedicated customer service professional with extensive experience in home loan industry. Solid team player with outgoing, positive demeanor and proven skills in establishing rapport with clients. Motivated to maintain customer satisfaction and contribute to company success. Specialize in quality, speed and process optimization. Articulate, energetic and results-oriented with exemplary passion for developing relationships, cultivating partnerships and growing businesses.

Work History summary

Assistant Credit Operation Manager IDFC First Bank Jaipur, Rajasthan- Feb 2022 -Current

Disbursement of Home Loan
Disbursement of Personal Loan
Disbursement of LAP
Disbursement OF ST-LAP Product
Original Papers Submission and Dispatch
Original Paper Closure Handover to the customer

Customer Relationship Executive HDFC LTD jaipur, Rajasthan - July 2017 – 15 Feb 2022 (HDFC SUPPORT ROLE)

Original property papers verification.

Submission of original property papers from lawyers, customers, Builders

PD in high value self employed case

Fixing and making of Direct purchase, Resale, Balance Transfer case, Builder purchase, Top up case, equity case, reach case etc

Increase/Decrease of the loan

Property selection on the system

Conversion of home loan rate

Part and full payment

Customer query and solution

Partial disbursement in case of construction cases

Fixing and making of insurance product

Add co applicant in loan

Process Associate Genpact India Pvt Ltd jaipur , Rajasthan - December 2016 - July 2017

Policy holder service Commission Banking of US process Handling the policy of US customer

Education summary

Institute Name

Swami Keshvanand Institute of Technology, management and Gramotham 2014-2016 (Master of Business administration)

College Name

S. S Jain Subodh College, Jaipur 2010-2013(Bachelor of Commerce)

School name

Sanjay Public School, Jaipur 2008-2010(Commerce)

Skills

Full knowledge of Home loan product
Customer Satisfaction
Good bonding with the sales executives
Fast working speed
Good communication Skills
Positive Attitude towards work
Team player

Additional Information

During 2020-21 annual closing in march help the Vaishali branch to Achieve 72 Crore disbursement in single month, with second highest disbursement Done by me.

During 2019-21 Vaishali branch has done the highest insurance disbursement in Rajasthan.

DOB-23/11/1992

Notice Period-Three month